

About

UX designer with a passion for problemsolving, people, and functionality. Has a diverse background in anthropology, nonprofits, and freelance design. Brings a unique and human-centered perspective to create efficient, effective, and empathetic design solutions.

Skills

- User Research
- User Interviews
- Enthography
- User Flows
- Information Architecture
- Personas
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Web and Graphic Design
- Branding and Marketing
- Empathy and Listening!

Tools

- Adobe XD
- Sketch
- InVision
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- In Design
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- GitHub

Education

CareerFoundry

UX Design Certificate Course

January 2020 - January 2021

University of California, San Diego B.A. in Sociocultural Anthropology with Honors

B.A. in Global Health

Class of 2017

Most Recent Project

QuickCare

Telehealth app • February -November 2020

- UX UI project completed for CareerFoundry course
- Taken from conception to hi-fi, clickable prototype
- Design thinking and iterative design processes

Professional Experience



🔆 Visual and Web Designer

Freelance • September 2019 - Present

- Collaborate with clients to identify business goals and design solutions
- Take designs from low-fidelity wireframes to live websites
- Research competitors and develop user personas



Visual and Web Designer

Telecom4Good • November 2017 - July 2019

- Manage pilot for refugee education program in Uganda
- Implementation and redesign of website
- Developing brand identity across visual assets



Caregiver and Household Manager

Private Residence • November 2014 -December 2019

- Organize, coordinate, and manage children's busy schedules
- Maintain smooth and efficient running of household
- Exercise consistent empathy and communication



Receptionist and Gallery Sitter

UCSD Visual Arts Department • April 2014 -December 2015

- Interacted with the public via phone and in-person
- Responsible for office management and scheduling
- Ensure smooth running of campus galleries

Volunteer Experience



Head Magician

Circle of Magic • May 2019 -Present

- Organize monthly meetings
- Empower women in their creative pursuits
- Listen and hold space for others to express



-★- Research Intern

San Diego County Center for TB Control • Sept 2016 -June 2017

- Planning of quantitative and qualitative research
- Conduct research and key informant interviews
- Synthesize and present findings as actionable recommendations for



Health Navigator Intern

Catholic Charities Diocese Refugee Resettlement and Health Services • November 2016 - June 2017

- Helped pilot new refugee mental health program
- Develop and design educational material
- Empathize and listen to experiences and needs of refugees

^{*}Proficient in French, Intermediate Spanish